SARABJIT BANSAL

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY Web Development Immersive Feb - May 2018

PUNJAB TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science 2004-2008

SKILLS

React.js, Ruby on Rails
PostgreSQL, SQL, Nokogiri
JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, three.js
HTML, CSS/SCCS
Git, Heroku
C++
Visual Studio. Visual Basic 6

CONTACT

P: 0432 854 277 E: sarabjit.bansal@gmail.com W: sarabjitbansal.github.io Full working rights in Australia

SOCIAL

linkedin.com/in/sarabjit-bansal github.com/SarabjitBansal instagram.com/SarabjitBansal

REFEREES

Available on request

ABOUT

I am a full-stack developer with strong programming skills making a return to the Digital/IT industry after moving from overseas.

Having worked for almost 6 years in the IT industry has given me strong coding etiquette along with project management and communication skills. I have brought myself up-to-date with the latest in tech and am looking forward to an exciting future in Digital/IT.

PROJECTS

CODERS APP - Find the right coders for your next project. Built on React.js & Ruby on Rails | Google Maps API | GitHub API | Geocoder

ECOSMART APP - Helps people make more sustainable choices in everyday life. Built on Ruby on Rails | Stripe | Nokogiri

 $\label{thm:healthy} \mbox{ HEALTHY FOOD APP - Find healthy recipes that will help in making changes to your food habits. Built on Ruby on Rails | Cloudinary | Regex$

TIC TAC TOE - The fun age old game of X's and 0's. Built in Javascript | Al

WORK EXPERIENCE

OPERATIONS MANAGER

Achieva Agents | Sep 2016 - Nov 2017

- · Creating and processing customer orders within SAP,
- Running reports and updating consignment details in databases

PROPERTY STYLIST

Uplift Interiors | Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

- Carrying out the installation of furniture and styling accessories,
- · Suggesting and integrating changes on the website

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING INTERN

Learning Fever | Jan 2015 - May 2015

- Produced recommendations report for promoting the website,
- Carry out competitor analysis and find keywords for SEO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Modern Software LLC | Feb 2009 - Nov 2014

- Designed and developed custom Assets, Budgeting, Finance, Fleet, Inventory & Purchasing modules in VB6 and Visual Studio,
- Carry out modification requests at client sites,
- Provided technical support and maintenance services